http://www.fundraising.com/about-us/privacy-policy

Fundraising.com
Privacy Policy
Last updated January 25, 2013
This privacy statement describes how Fundraising.com collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: Fundraising.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.
This Privacy Statement is effective as of the date written above and is designed to meet the following principles and practices:
We fully disclose what information is collected on our sites and how we use that information;
Campaign organizers, participants and supporters who participate in our online campaign programs may choose whether they want to continue to receive communications from us;
We provide our registered campaign organizers with access to their account information and the ability to modify that information; and
We are dedicated to creating a secure environment for user information and use an advanced network server security system to safeguard user information.
In the more detailed description of our privacy practices below, when we use the term "you," we are referring to registered campaign organizers, participants, supporters and general users of our web sites who order campaign products or information from our web sites. When we use the term "personal information," we are referring to user's first and last name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address. Fundraising.com does not collect social security numbers.
Violating our privacy policy is cause for termination of your campaign. In addition, Fundraising.com reserves the right to cooperate with municipal, state and federal officials in any law-enforcement investigation requiring either personal information or reports about lawful or unlawful user activities on this site.
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. Registration Information In order to use our services, and/or to receive a free information kit, campaign organizers must complete an online registration form or call our toll-free number at 1-800-561-8388. When registering online or by phone, campaign organizers need to supply contact information, relevant affiliation(s), and details related to their fundraising campaign, such as their first name, last name, group name, email address, phone number and physical mailing address. We collect this information from fundraising campaign organizers to assess the organizer's fundraising needs and to respond to them with information relevant to their request.
We use their first and last names to personalize users’ fundraising.com access. We use email address to contact users, if necessary. We use the campaign organizers mailing address to send profit checks and their phone number to contact them when requested. Some information, that is not of a personal nature, such as which browser you are using (Internet Explorer, Netscape, etc.), the operating system you are using (Windows, Mac Os, etc.) and your domain name (IP address) or Internet provider, may be collected. This information will be used in statistical analyses of site usage. It helps us improve and personalize our service and content to better meet your needs and make the site more enjoyable, efficient and secure to use.
Order Information
To purchase or order sample campaign products through any of our sites, you will need to provide order information (which may include credit card information). If you are purchasing campaign products from us, once your credit card has been approved by our third-party transactional company for the amount equaling the total of the supporter's desired purchases, the third-party supplier(s) will receive all relevant purchase details (item description, quantity, etc.) needed to fulfill the order. All personal information collected during the ordering process is used for order processing, billing and shipping.
Information Sharing
We will not rent or share your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for their promotional purposes. As detailed above, Fundraising.com does not give your personal information to third parties not associated with our campaign products or services. Our third-party suppliers use a variety of external delivery companies to ship orders, and a third-party firm processes the campaign supporters' credit cards for goods purchased. These companies, by contractual agreement with us, are not permitted to retain, store or use personally identifiable customer information except for order processing and fulfillment.
Data Retention
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at online@fundraising.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Tell-A-friend
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Fundraising.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. If you receive an email inviting you to visit our site, this email was initiated by the Fundraising campaign manager and not by Fundraising.com. Fundraising supporters may also receive reminder emails about the fundraising campaign. To unsubscribe from these emails, simply click on the Email Preferences link at the bottom of the email in question and update your preferences or contact us at 1-800-561-8388 or online@fundraising.com. The use of all email addresses is limited to the fundraising campaign; see acceptable use section below for more details. Your friend may contact us at online@fundraising.com to request that we remove this information from our database.
Log Files and Cookies
Cookies are a small line of text generated by a site's server and sent to a user's browser, which enable the browser and server to better communicate with each other. We use cookies to analyze traffic patterns, for statistical analysis, to enhance your navigation of our web site, to tailor Web content, and to track login names, passwords and click stream data. We do not use cookies to track your navigation and usage of other web sites on the Internet. The only log information collected is non-personally identifying data, such as time and date of a web visit, the browser and operating system being used, the IP address or domain name of the user's ISP, and the web URL a user linked from. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie and you can refuse to accept cookies. Refusing to accept an Fundraising.com cookie may disable some enhanced navigation features that our cookies provide, but will not disable you from using the fundraising.com web site.
Third Party Cookies
The use of cookies by our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] is/is not covered by our privacy statement. We do/do not have access or control over these cookies. Our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] use session ID cookies [to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the shopping cart, etc.]
Widgets
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
Surveys & Contests
All surveys generated by Fundraising.com are distributed with detailed information concerning the reason for the survey, the nature of the information that will be collected and the manner in which the information will be used.
Campaign Information and Newsletters
Fundraising.com may periodically contact you by phone, mail or e-mail to inform you of campaign products and services. If you do not wish to receive further communications from us, you may opt-out by using the unsubscribe option in our e-mail correspondence, calling our toll-free number at 1-800-561-8388, or by sending an e-mail to online@fundraising.com to be removed from the e-mail list.
Accessing and Updating Your Information
For online fundraising campaigns, campaign organizers may access and modify or delete their account information by accessing their account profiles using their user ID and password. Supporters may request any changes by calling our toll-free number at: 1-800-561-8388, or by sending an e-mail to online@fundraising.com.
Security
Fundraising.com realizes that a secure online environment is of utmost importance to protect your personal and financial information. We take strong security precautions both online and offline. All credit card information we collect online is encrypted using Secure Socket Layers (SSL) technology, a leading advanced network server security system. We decrypt the information only at the point of processing through Fundraising.com’s ordering system, further ensuring the security of your information. In order to protect your data offline, Fundraising.com’s employee access to sensitive information is restricted, and only authorized personnel may access specific information as needed. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Acceptable Use
fundraising.com is to be used only for fundraising campaigns. Fundraising.com reserves the right to terminate any campaign, including all e-mail access to the campaign account, if we determine that the campaign may be illegal, unethical, misleading or in contravention of any federal, state or municipal laws, regulations or bylaws.
E-Mail Restrictions
Fundraising.com is committed to responsible Internet commerce. We do not tolerate use of the fundraising.com system for non-campaign e-mails or any e-mail that includes material that Fundraising.com, in its sole discretion, deems inappropriate. Sending non-fundraising or inappropriate e-mail from a fundraising.com account is cause for immediate termination of access to that account.
Links to Other Sites
Fundraising.com contains links to other sites on the Internet. Although Fundraising.com is diligent about the selection of its partners and affiliates, we are neither responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites or any other sites you may visit on the Internet. For your own information and security, we recommend that you carefully read a site's individual privacy policies prior to using that site.
Changes to the Fundraising.com Privacy Statement
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
Contacting the Web Site
We strive to do everything we can to protect the privacy of our users. Please feel free to share any comments and concerns with us. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact: Fundraising.com, 205 West Service Road, Champlain, NY 12919.
�
How do you want your guide?
Request your Digital guide?
Care to Tell us More?
Sending your information...
"Opps! There was a problem submitting form! Please call us 1.800.443.5353"
Step 2
How much do you want to raise?
Group Name
What are you raising funds for?
2 / 6
Next
"Opps! There was a problem submitting form! Please call us 1.800.443.5353"
Armed Forces Americas (except Canada)
Armed Forces (Africa, Canada, Europe, Middle East)
"Opps! There was a problem submitting form! Please call us 1.800.443.5353"
Step 4
How many people are in your group?
What type of group are you?
Back
4 / 6
Next
"Opps! There was a problem submitting form! Please call us 1.800.443.5353"
One last thing
Help us personalize your experience
How soon are you planning to get started?
"Opps! There was a problem submitting form! Please call us 1.800.443.5353"
Congratulations!
You are all done and well on your way to a successful fundraiser
